Curriculum Vitae

Lewis Skellett

Personal Details:

Lewis Skellett 207 Mountcastle Crescent, Edinburgh, EH8 7SX

Email: Lewis.Skellett@gmail.com Phone: (+44) 07552686893

Profile

I am a highly motivated final year Creative Computing Global student, with the experience in multiple programming languages and technologies. With skills in event planning, team leadership, and critical thinking gained through work experience and volunteer opportunities on top of the time spent in university. I was also given the chance to study aboard at the Copenhagen School of Design and Technology (KEA) which improved my ability to adapt to new situations and allowed me to learn about other cultures.

Education

<u>BSci (Hons) in Creative Computing Global</u> <u>Edinburgh Napier University</u>

Modules undertaken during third year:

- Digital Storytelling
 - o How to create stories and characters for digital stories, persona creation for testing
- Advanced Web Technologies
 - Python/Flask web Development using Jinja 2 and bootstrap in a Linux environment
- Scripting for Interactive Media
 - o UX and Design based web design and development module

Modules undertaken during Semester aboard at KEA:

- Marketing and Communication
 - o Analyse, develop and implement marketing concepts with a focus on Omnichannel marketing
- E-Commerce
 - Digital Commerce involving strategic considerations, optimisation and management of solutions
- Project Management
 - 24 hour group project to simulate a "Work Crunch". Developed a small viral marketing campaign

Modules undertaken in fourth Year:

- Creative Computing
 - Creative use of all computer skills, Creating interactive artwork for a collaborative museum exhibit
- User Experience
 - History and progression of User Experience overall, how to put the concepts into practice and how to study their effects of different user experience solutions.
- Professional Identity through Portfolio Development
 - Module focused on assisting the transition from student to professional
- Honours Project
 - Research into "TwitchPlaysPokemon" internet phenomenon and testing to see the effects of group based decision making in Video Games.

Curriculum Vitae

Portobello High School

Advanced Higher

- Computing
- Graphic Communication

Higher

- Math
- Music

Intermediate 2

• English

Technical Skills

Programming:

HTML, CSS, JavaScript

Arduino, Processing, Max MSP

Python

Java

Media:

Adobe Photoshop
Adobe Illustrator

Adobe Premiere

MS Office Suite

Work Experience

BronyScot, Committee Member: Co-Chair, Head of Technologies: 2014 - Present

- Responsible for the hiring, Set-up and running of Audio and Visual Technologies
- Head of the team that run the technologies for the event
- Responsible for quickly training team members in technologies they had not used.
- Responsible for part of the PR and advertising for the event
- Helps raising funds for charities, including The Scottish Association for Mental Health and The Children's Hospice Association Scotland

Morrison's, Checkout operator: August 2014 - January 2016

- Operating the checkout while authorising the sale of age restricted products
- Supervising cleaning, fixing and authorising sales on the self-checkouts
- Tidying and refilling shelves as well as cleaning floors and equipment

Peacocks, Store Colleague: August 2010 – January 2012, June 2012 – August 2014

- Operating the checkout while authorising returns
- Ensuring the store is clean and tidy at throughout the day
- Stocktaking in store and in the warehouse
- Helping customers find what they may be looking for and/or helping them find replacements

Lyceum Youth Theatre, Sound Tech: January 2009 – March 2013

- Responsible for the recording and editing Sound effects for stage performances
- Responsible for operating the sound board during rehearsals and live shows at various theatres including The Edinburgh Lyceum Theatre and The Traverse Theatre

Hobbies and Interests

- Working with and using new technologies
- Writing and performing Music including playing in a band for live events
- Enjoying craft ales at Festivals around Scotland
- Enjoy Going out for Coffees with friends
- Computers and computer gaming
- Member of the Edinburgh Napier University Anime Society
- Gym Member